<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Droid Wall</string>
    <string name="title_enabled">Droid Wall</string>
    <string name="title_disabled">Droid Wall (Firewall disabled)</string>
    <string name="showrules">Show rules</string>
    <string name="applyrules">Apply rules</string>
    <string name="purgerules">Purge rules</string>
    <string name="setpwd">Set password</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="enable_fw">Enable Firewall</string>
    <string name="disable_fw">Disable Firewall</string>
    <string name="pass_titleset">Set password lock</string>
    <string name="pass_titleget">Password required</string>
    <string name="enterpass">Enter the password:</string>
    <string name="enternewpass">Enter the new password (leave blank to remove):</string>
	<string name="help_dialog_text"><i>Author: Rodrigo Zechin Rosauro</i>
		\n<i><a href="http://droidwall.googlecode.com">http://droidwall.googlecode.com</a></i>
		\n
		\n<i>Droid Wall - Android Firewall</i> is a front-end application for the powerful <b>iptables</b> Linux firewall.
		It allows you to restrict which applications are permitted to access your data networks.
		\nThis is the perfect solution if you don't have an unlimited data plan, or just wants to see your battery lasting longer.
		\n<b>Using Droid Wall:</b>
		\n<b>1.</b> Click on <b>Network Interfaces</b> to select which interfaces should be blocked.
		\n<b>2.</b> Click on <b>Mode</b> to switch between <i>White List</i> and <i>Black List</i> modes.
		\n<b>3.</b> Mark the applications that you want to block or allow (depending on the selected mode).
		\n<b>4.</b> Open the menu and click on <b>Apply rules</b> to modify your iptables rules.
		\n<b>Note:</b> After applying the rules, they will be saved and automatically restored every-time you restart your phone.
		\n
		\n<b>Other features:</b>
		\nClick on <b>Show rules</b> menu to display current iptables rules output.
		\n
		\nClick on <b>Disable Firewall</b> menu to completely disable the Firewall.
		You must manually enable the Firewall later by clicking on <b>Enable Firewall</b>.
		\n
		\n<b>Password lock:</b>
		\nYou can set a password lock for Droid Wall by using the <b>Set password</b> menu option.
		To remove the password protection, just reset it to blank.
	</string>
</resources>
